Andrew Lawn

860-514-0587 • Lawna12@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Experienced, energetic and sales-minded hospitality worker. Very reliable, with 15+ years restaurant experience, 18+ years sales and customer service. Business ownership experience allows a big-picture view of process and policies. Positive attitude and strong work ethic. Focus on contribution to employer success.

SKILL SET

- Management
- Sales
- Customer Service
- Natural Upselling Ability

- Cost Awareness
- Networking
- Community Building
- Adept to Change

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Pizzetta, Bartender/Manager

May 2015 - Present

- Consistent and accurate pours of all alcohols and mixers.
- Excellent bar area control & monitoring of client intoxication levels while maintaining a fun atmosphere.
- Assisted with creation of cocktail menus and drink specials.
- Inventory control
- Training and development of new bartenders and servers.
- Assisted in implementing Pizzetta from a wine and beer bar to full service bar.

KeyBank, Mortgage Loan Originator

February 2017 – November 2017

- Analysis of credit, character and financial information to find a fit between client and prospective lender.
- Networking for potential relationships between mortgage lender and real estate brokers.

ACL Estate Service, Owner/Manager

November 2015 – November 2016

- Managed a crew of laborers for de-clutters, liquidations, and photography.
- Knowing when to call in an appraiser for higher end items and which venue would best support its
 market
- Management of payroll, advertising, balancing banks for liquidations. Correct analysis for job bids to include labor hours, materials, taxes, dumpster/storage container needs and liquidation potential.

Primary Residential Mortgage, Inc. Business Growth/Loan Officer

March 2014 - June 2015

Wireless Zone, Sales Team Lead

October 2010 - March 2014

- Customer service approach led to many repeat customers and substantial referral business.
- Consistently hit above sales mark objectives. Multiple sales contest winner, franchise wide.
- Competence, work ethic, and motivation made it possible to take on management related challenges beyond my level of assignment, including but not limited to opening and closing duties, overview of daily sales, ordering and organization of inventory, reporting nightly store sales numbers, and
- Assisted and trained other team members.

EDUCATION

BS, Business Administration/Finance, Southern Connecticut State University

May 2009

Technical Skills: Proficient with MS Word, Excel, PowerPoint. Gadget, Internet and research savvy.

PROFESSIONAL NETWORKING

- Membership and leadership committee/Closing visitor host, Seaport BNI Chapter Mystic, Connecticut. March 2011-2016
- Co-chair Professional Development Committee, S.E. CT Young Professionals Network. Member since 2014 Co-chair for 2016
- S.E. CT Chair, Southern Connecticut State Uni. Alumni Association 2015 present